broadbandtvnews.com 2019-12-16

# Our Privacy Policy – Terms and Conditions

By using this site you acknowledge your acceptance to the terms and conditions specified below.

Broadband TV News LLP is not responsible for the content of any external internet websites that are linked to this site.

The contents of Broadband TV News LLP are copyright. Any part of this site may not be copied, reproduced or republished without the written consent of Broadband TV News LLP. You may share content via the social functions.

While Broadband TV News LLP makes every effort to ensure the information contained in this website is accurate at the time of publication, Broadband TV News LLP do not accept any liability for any errors or omissions.

Broadband TV News LLP do not endorse or warrant the quality of products and services provided by companies advertising on this site. Broadband TV News LLP cannot be held liable for any a loss arising from use, information or profit, whether negligent or tortous arising from use of this site.

Where our site contains links to other sites and resources provided by third parties, these links are provided for your information only. We have no control over the contents of those sites or resources, and accept no responsibility for them or for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of them. When accessing a site via our website we advise you check their terms of use and privacy policies to ensure compliance and determine how they may use your information.

These terms and conditions shall be governed in accordance of the laws of England and Wales.

* * *

**Our Privacy Policy**

Broadband TV News LLP will be what’s known as the ‘Controller’ of the personal data you provide to us. We only collect basic personal data about you which does not include any special types of information or location based information. This does however include name, address, email, company, and job description.

_Why we need your data_  
We need to know your basic personal data in order to provide you with our daily and weekly news services as well as relevant marketing messages in line with this overall contract. We will not collect any personal data from you we do not need in order to provide and oversee this service to you. 

_Our website_  
When someone visits www.broadbandtvnews.com we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website.

_Our mailing list_  
As part of the registration process for our newsletters, we collect personal information. We use that information for a couple of reasons: to tell you about stuff you’ve asked us to tell you about; to contact you if we need to obtain or provide additional information; to check our records are right and to check every now and then that you’re happy and satisfied. We don’t rent or trade email lists with other organisations and businesses.  
We use a third-party provider, MailChimp, to deliver our newsletter. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our e-newsletter. For more information, please see [MailChimp’s privacy notice](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/). You can unsubscribe to our mailings at any time of the day or night by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our emails or by emailing admin@broadbandtvnews.com

_Why did you receive a mailing from us?_  
Our email marketing is permission based. If you received a mailing from us, our records indicate that (a) you have expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future (“opt-in”), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.

If you believe you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to admin@broadbandtvnews.com for review.

_How can you stop receiving email from us?_  
Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the SafeUnsubscribe or Update Profile links at the end of any email.

_How we protect your privacy_  
We use appropriate security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.

_Sharing and Usage_  
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone for their promotional use without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information, and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.

However, from time to time we do send so-called ‘partnermailings’ from third parties to our database of subscribers. We always use our own mailing service provider for these mailings and never make the actual addresses available to any third-party. We send these promotional mailings – as well as banner advertising on our website and in our newsletters – in order to finance our daily news service, which is completely free of charge to our readers.

_Use of Web Beacons_  
When we send you emails, we may include a web beacon to allow us to determine the number of people who open our emails. When you click on a link in an email, we may record this individual response to allow us to customize our offerings to you. Web beacons collect only limited information, such as a cookie identifier, time and date of a page being viewed, and a description of the page on which the Web Beacon resides (the URL).

Web Beacons can be refused when delivered via email. If you do not wish to receive Web Beacons via email, you will need to disable HTML images or refuse HTML (select Text only) emails via your email software.

_Events registration_  
When you order a ticket (or tickets) for one of our events online your name, address data, email and contact number will be stored in the third party system we are using, Eventbrite. Please be assured that we do not share your personal details with any other company without your consent. For more information, please see [Eventbrite’s privacy notice.](https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/support/articles/en_US/Troubleshooting/eventbrite-privacy-policy?lg=en_GB)

_What we do with your data_  
All the personal data we process is processed by our staff in the European Union, however for the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance this information is located on servers within the United States. No third parties have access to your personal data unless the law allows them to do so. 

_How long we keep your data_  
We are required under UK tax law to keep your basic personal data (name, address, contact details) for a minimum of 6 years after which time it will be destroyed. Your information we use for marketing purposes will be kept with us until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information. 

_What are your rights_  
If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect you can request to see this information and have it corrected or deleted. If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact us to have the matter investigated. admin@broadbandtvnews.com

If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are processing your personal data not in accordance with the law you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office <https://ico.org.uk/>

* * *

Broadband TV News LLP is a company registered in England and Wales. Registered Number: OC351738. VAT Registration No: 984 3863 68

Registered Office: 10 Wellington Street, Cambridge CB1 1HW
